[
  {
    "question": "What is JS ?",
    "answer_1": "Lipstick",
    "answer_2": "Pen",
    "answer_3": "Hair-cut",
    "answer_4": "Programming-language",
    "correct": "Programming-language"
  },
  {
    "question": "The full name of JS is ?",
    "answer_1": "Jason-Statham",
    "answer_2": "Juicy-Soup",
    "answer_3": "Jennifer-Smith",
    "answer_4": "Java-Script",
    "correct": "Java-Script"
  },
  {
    "question": "The JS is singl-threaded language ?",
    "answer_1": "Yes",
    "answer_2": "No",
    "answer_3": "both",
    "answer_4": "none",
    "correct": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does singl-threade mean ?",
    "answer_1": "to deal with one operation",
    "answer_2": "to deal with multipul operations",
    "answer_3": "an oop feature",
    "answer_4": "json syntax",
    "correct": "to deal with one operation"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is API ?",
    "answer_1": "application programming interface",
    "answer_2": "banana",
    "answer_3": "cow",
    "answer_4": "an anime serios",
    "correct": "application programming interface"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JSON ?",
    "answer_1": "actor",
    "answer_2": "player",
    "answer_3": "recieve & send data",
    "answer_4": "Programming-language",
    "correct": "recieve & send data"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Ajax ?",
    "answer_1": "aproach",
    "answer_2": "second virsion of json",
    "answer_3": "rocket",
    "answer_4": "country",
    "correct": "aproach"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do Promise & Fetch do the same job ?",
    "answer_1": "Yes",
    "answer_2": "No",
    "answer_3": "both",
    "answer_4": "half-yes",
    "correct": "half-yes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is DOM ?",
    "answer_1": "Document Object Model",
    "answer_2": "bla",
    "answer_3": "bla",
    "answer_4": "bla bla bla",
    "correct": "Document Object Model"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is BOM ?",
    "answer_1": "diddly-squat",
    "answer_2": "Browser Object Model",
    "answer_3": "song",
    "answer_4": "onion",
    "correct": "Browser Object Model"
  }
]
